好了 不准偷看
All right, no peeking. No peeking.
不许偷看!
No peeking. No peeking!
好吧 不过我睁开眼睛时 你最好穿着衣服
All right, all right, but you better be wearing clothes when I open my eyes.
好了 睁开眼睛
All right. Open your eyes!
妈妈咪呀 我的老天
Sweet mother of all that is good and pure.
不错吧 "我们的日子" 跟我续约了
Huh? "Days of Our Lives" picked up my option!
恭喜啊!      对啊!
Congratulations!        I know!
现在我们总算能像样地看 "绿色田野" 了
Now we can finally watch Green Acres the way it was meant to be seen.
哪一张是我的
So uh, which one is mine?
你爱坐哪张就哪张
Whichever one you want, man, whichever one you want!
那张不行
Not that one.
噢 爽
Oh, yes!
噢 爽啊 这才叫生活
Oh, yeah! That's the stuff.
来吗
Do we dare?
来啊
We dare.
噢
Oh!
爽啊!
【海盗美剧 友情制作】
-== http://www.hdmeiju.com ==-
新浪微博：@海盗美剧
《老友记》蓝光版 第02季 第15集
罗斯和瑞秋 The One Where Rachel and Ross.. You Know
调校制作：寒 枫
字幕编辑：yjchandler
真不敢相信两头牛做出这么大的牺牲
I can't believe two cows made the ultimate sacrifice
只是为了让你们翘起二郎腿来看电视
so you guys could watch TV with your feet up.
不 它们是椅子形状的牛
No, they were chair-shaped cows.
反正它们在野外也难逃贝爷之口
They never would have survived in the wild.
这屏幕太炫了
This screen is amazing.
迪克凡・戴克看起来跟真人一样大      对啊
I mean Dick Van Dyke is practically life-size.        Uh-huh
哇哦!
Woah!
萝丝・玛丽不该上这么大的屏幕 是吧
Rose Marie really belongs on a smaller screen, doesn't she?
嗨 各位      嘿
Hi, you guys.        Hey.
嘿
Hey.
嘿 亲爱的      嘿
Hey, you.        Hey, you.
喂 别挡着电视      烦死了
Whoa, hey, whoa.        Oh.
今天怎么样
So, uh, how was your day?
和平时差不多 风和日丽 莺歌燕舞
Oh, you know, pretty much the usual, uh, sun shining, birds chirping.
真的? 我也是
Really? Mine too.
酷啊 我也是
Hey, cool! Mine too!
好烦呐
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
我得去馆里一趟
I gotta get to the museum.
那么 今晚见
So, um... I'll see you tonight?
好的
Okay.
再见 各位      再见      再见
Bye guys.        Bye.        Bye.
今晚?
Tonight?
喂 喂
Hey, yo.
今晚怎么了
What's tonight?
今晚是我们第一次正式约会
It is our first official date.
第一次约会
Our first date.
哈罗
Uh, ha, ha. Hello?
嗨
Hi.
今晚你该在我主持的外烩上当跑堂的
Tonight, you're supposed to waitress for me? My catering thing?
想起来了吗      天啊 摩妮卡 我忘了!
Any of that trigger anything for you?        God, oh God, Monica. I forgot!
这是我们的第一次约会
This is our first date.
但这事是我妈帮我介绍的
Yes, but my mom got me this job.
我可以来当服务生 真的 我可以
Okay, I can be a waitress, I can be a waitress!
哦 谢谢 太感谢了 看 菲比可以
Oh, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you. See? Phoebe! Phoebe!
真的吗 菲比 你得真的当服务生
Really, Pheebs? Because, you know, you'd have to be an actual waitress.
这不是像 "我可以办家庭酒会" 之类的
This can't be like your "I can be a bear cub" thing.
我可以当服务生 看好了
I can be a waitress. Okay, watch this.
给我两份一号餐 培根要86分熟
Um, give me two number ones, 86 the bacon
一份熏肉炒蛋吐司
one Adam and Eve on a raft and wreck them!
是007!
It's James Bond!
抱歉来迟了
Sorry we're late.
没关系 请进
Ah, that's okay. Come on in.
对不起 摩妮卡盖勒来不来 我听说她要来
Um, I'm sorry, is Monica Geller coming? I was told she was.
柏克医生 我就是
Dr.Burke, it's, it's me.
摩妮卡?
Monica?
天啊 你以前好...
My God! You used to be so...
我是说你... 你一定减了...
I mean, you... you, you, you must have lost like...
你漂亮极了
You look great.
谢啦
Thanks, thank you.
这是我朋友菲比 今晚她帮我
This is my friend Phoebe. She'll be helping me tonight.
菲比 幸会
Hi, Phoebe, nice to meet you.
近来如何
So how you been?
我很好 你呢
I've been great, just great. How have you been?
噢 你大概也知道我跟芭芭拉分手了
Oh, well obviously you know Barbara and I split up
不然你不会来歪头那一招
otherwise you wouldn't have done the head tilt.
歪头?
The head tilt?
对 自从离婚之后 当别人向我问好时
Yeah, since the divorce, when anybody asks me how I am
他们总是同情地歪着头问 "你好吗 不要紧吧"
it's always with a sympathetic head tilt. "How you doing? You okay?"
哦
Oh.
对不起
I'm sorry.
不 没关系 相信我 我也一样
No, no, it's, it's fine, believe me, I do it too.
我总是点头示意 "我没事"
I always answer with the "I'm okay" head bob. "I'm okay."
"你确定?" "对 我没事"
"You're sure?" "Yeah, I'm fine."
我得去放音乐了 我买了个新的CD换片机
Hey listen, I gotta set up the music. I got a new CD changer.
当然了 离婚后我只剩四张CD可换了
Of course, the divorce only left me with four CDs to change.
噢      真惨
Oh.        That's too bad.
死不了的
I'll survive.
"沃德 反身上篮"
"Ward. With a reverse."
两份大的 都要多加起司
Uh, two larges, extra cheese on both.
听着
But listen...
不要按19号的门铃
don't ring the buzzer for 19.
按20号 盖勒与葛林的门铃
Ring 20. GeIler/Green.
她们会开门的 懂?
They'll let you in, okay?
按我们的门铃就没小费
If you buzz our door, there's no tip for you.
好 谢了
Okay, thanks.
披萨马上就来 我说不用起来吧
Pizza's on the way. I told you we wouldn't have to get up.
如果要尿尿呢
What if we have to pee?
我来把汽水退了
I'll cancel the sodas.
你得进去 这是你的派对
You've got to get back out there. It's your party!
但是眼科医生都很无聊啊
But they're so dull, they're all ophthalmologists.
你不也是眼科医生
You're an ophthalmologist.
那只是因为我父母要我当医生 我本来想当警长的
Only because my parents wanted me to be. I wanted to be a sheriff.
呵呵 真好笑 白内衣 白内障 我懂了
Ha, ha, that's funny, no, Cadillac, cataract, I get it, no I get it
待那儿别动!
But you stay out there!
看到没
You see?
好吧 这样
All right, I tell you what.
五分钟后我来找你 就说烤肉霸出了问题
I'll come get you in five minutes with some sort of, um, kebab emergency.
好吧
Okay.
但愿管用
Ah. You better
壮士一去不复返
Oh, God, here we go.
嘿 要看他们发神经吗
Hey, want to see them go nuts?
看好了
Watch this.
谁要杯子
Who needs glasses?
你被迷晕了
You are so smitten.
我才没有
I am not!
你是只神魂颠倒的小猫咪
Oh, you are so much the smitten kitten.
噢
Oh.
你该约他出去
You should ask him out.
柏克医生?
Dr.Burke?
我可不这么想 我是说 他太成熟了
I don't think so. I mean, like, he's a grownup.
那又怎样 你们两个彼此都有好感
So? You two are totally into each other.
菲比 他是我爸妈的朋友 他差不多比我大二十岁
Phoebe, he's a friend of my parents. He's like 20 years older than me.
那你就再也不跟他见面了?
OK, so, what, you're just never gonna see him again?
也不能那么说
Not never.
我约他明天帮我检查眼睛
I mean, I'm gonna see him tomorrow at my eye appointment.
你不是才检查过吗
Didn't you like, just get your eyes checked?
是啊 但是
Well yeah, but, you know, uh
27岁是个应该多注意眼睛的年龄
27 is a... dangerous eye age.
别这样嘛 我不是说这部电影不好看
C'mon, I'm not saying it was a bad movie.
我的意思是 这有点
I'm just saying, you know, it was a little. . .
难懂
hard to follow.
我说过会有字幕的
I told you there was going to be subtitles.
我知道
I know.
我只是不想 第一次约会戴着眼镜
I just didn't want to wear my glasses on our first date.
摩妮卡
Monica?
接吻的时候拜托不要喊出我妹妹的名字啊
It would really help when I'm kissing if you didn't shout my sister's name.
亲爱的 我只是在试探      噢
Honey, I'm just checking.        Oh.
摩妮卡      摩妮卡
Monica?        Mon?
摩妮卡
Monica?
怎么了
What?
怎么了      对不起
What?        I'm sorry.
天呐 真对不起 只是当你的手滑到我屁股上时
Oh God, I'm sorry, it's just, when you moved your hands down to my butt
我就想到 "喔噢! 罗斯在摸我屁股!"
it was like, "Whoa! Ross's hands are on my butt!"
抱歉
Sorry.
很好笑 为什么呢
And that's, that's funny. Why?
不 不好笑
Well, it's not, uh...
我是说 抱歉 我猜是有点紧张
I mean, I'm sorry. I guess I'm just nervous.
毕竟是你啊
I mean, it's you.
是我们啊      嗯
You know, it's us.        Mm.
我们在越过那条线 这是件大事
I mean we're crossing that line. It's sort of a big thing.
我知道 我只是不知道大到让你发笑
I, I know it's big. I just didn't know it was uh, ha-ha big.
好啦
Okay.
好吧 我的手离你屁股还很远
Okay, my hands were nowhere near your butt.
我知道
I know, I know, I know, I know!
抱歉 我只是想到上次你的手在那儿游荡
I was just thinking about when they were there the last time, I'm sorry.
真是太抱歉了 好了 好了 这样 我保证会乖
I'm sorry, I'm sorry. Okay, okay, look, woah, I promise.
我不会再笑了
I'm good, I'm not gonna laugh anymore.
好了 把你的手放回去
Okay, put your hands back there.
不 现在换我不行了 因为我觉得太不自然了
No see now, now I can't because uh, I'm feeling too self conscious.
就摸半边
Just one cheek.
不了 感觉没了
Nuh, uh, the moment's gone.
把手伸出来 我自己贴上来
Alright, alright, just put your hands out and I'll back up into them.
那可真 "浪漫"
That's romantic.
来吧 摸一下      不要
C'mon touch it.        No.
来嘛 捏一下        不
Oh, come on, squeeze it.        No!
揉呢      不要
Rub it?        No.
快点抓住老娘的屁股!
Oh, come on! Would you just grab my ass?
看 车子起火了
Wow, look at that, the car is on fire
但上面昂贵的烤漆
yet somehow its expensive paint job
在奇迹蜡的保护下完好无损
is protected by the Miracle Wax.
老兄 你脸上粘了个奇多
You got a Cheeto on your face, man.
谢了
Thanks.
嘿      嘿
Hey.        Hey.
你来这儿干嘛 不是要跟瑞秋出去吗
What are you doing here? Aren't you supposed to be out with Rachel?
那是14个小时前的事
That was 14 hours ago.
结果如何
So how'd it go?
怎么说呢
Oh...
听着 你们有没有过跟一个女孩亲热的时候
Listen, have you ever been uh, you know, fooling around with a girl
她却笑了起来
and, uh, she started laughing?
有啊 不过那是1982年
Yeah, but, uh, it was 1982
哥的瀑布发型让她的下巴发痒
and my Flock of Seagulls haircut was tickling her chin.
她对你笑了?
She laughed at you?
嗯 从九年级的打字课开始我就在憧憬这一刻了
Yeah. I don't know, I've been wanting this since like ninth grade typing.
我只是希望一切能完美
You know, and I just want it to be perfect
顺利...
and... right and...
激光束为什么不会穿透烤漆啊
Why isn't that laser beam cutting through the paint?
因为有了奇迹蜡      绝对是个奇迹
It's the Miracle Wax!        It certainly is a miracle.
嗨 伙计们      嘿
Hi, you guys.        Hey.
嘿      嗨
Hey.        Hi.
听着 我在想
Listen, I was, um, thinking about...
听着 你们能大声点吗
Listen, can you guys uh, speak up?
你们那么小声 真的很难听清楚
It's harder for us to hear you when you lower your voice.
好吧 听我说
Okay, listen
昨晚的事我很抱歉 我真的很想补偿你
I'm sorry about last night, and I really want to make it up to you.
不 你不用补偿我...
No, you, you know, there's no need to make it up...
怎么个补偿法
How?
我在想 或许来顿浪漫的晚餐
Well, I was thinking maybe a, um, a romantic dinner
烛光 美酒
with, um, candles and wine.
或许 呃 回我那里
and then, uh, maybe going back to my place
来点甜点
for, um, dessert.
嗯
Hmm.
听起来...
That sounds...
很完美
I don't... perfect?
这怎么回事
What's this?
能帮忙买几瓶啤酒吗
Would you get us a couple of beers?
现在我要检查你的眼睛了
I'm going to look into your eyes now.
真的吗
Really?
对啊 我就是干这个的
Yeah, that's my job.
好 向上看
All right, look up.
向下看
Look down.
张开眼睛 向下看
Now, open your eyes and look down.
好的
That's right.
看着光
Look into the light.
现在看着我
Now look at me.
好的
Okay.
你的眼睛看起来不错 非常健康
Your eyes look good. Those are good eyes.
很好 感觉不错
Good. They feel good.
我是说在我脸上
In my head.
呃 那么
Um, so...
见到你真好      彼此
It was great to see you.        You too.
我也是
You too.
好吧 那
Okay, um...
再见
Goodbye.
眼药水!      什么?
Drops!        What?
眼药水 来 免费的
Drops. Here, they're free.
谢谢 呃
Thanks. Uh so...
我最好还是走吧
I guess I better be going.
好吧 改天见
Oh, okay, yeah, I'll see you later.
谢谢
Thanks again.
我们得把你们两只懒猪弄起来
We have to get you lazy boys out of these chairs.
喂喂喂      好吧
Hey, whoa, hey, whoa.        Oh, oh.
你们应该出去走走 到真实世界去
You know you should go outside and be with the three-dimensional people.
不 家里很好
No. Inside good.
外面太逊了
Outside bad.
你们真是太可悲了
You guys are so pathetic.
"仙纳度"!
Oh Xanadu!
太好了
Oh!
她入会了
She's one of us now.
嗨 伙计们      嘿
Hi, you guys.        Hey.
嘿      嘿
Hey.        Hey.
我们只是想过来跟各位道晚安
Well we just wanted to stop by and, uh, say good night.
晚安      晚安
Good night.        Good night.
瞧瞧 他们连头都不回
Look at that, they won't even turn their heads.
好 各位 我要脱上衣了
Alright you guys, I'm taking off my shirt.
她唬人呢
Naa, she's lying.
别再把吃的送到我们家了
Stop sending food to our apartment!
打扮得这么漂亮干嘛
Well, why are you dressed up?
今晚不是只有你们有约会哦
You're not the only one who has a date tonight.
什么 你有约会 跟谁
What? You have a date? Who with?
你不认识的
No one.
乖嘛 他叫什么
Come on, what's his name?
没有名字
Nothing.
乖 听话 告诉哥
Come on, tell me.
好吧 但我真的很期待这次约会 懂吗
All right, but I'm very excited about this, okay?
你得保证不会摆出大哥的架子来教训我
So you gotta promise you won't get all big-brothery and judgmental.
我保证 快说是谁
Oh, I promise. What?
是理查柏克
It's Richard Burke.
理查柏克是谁
Who's Richard Burke?
柏克医生?
Doc, Doctor Burke?
你要跟柏克医生约会? 为什么...
You have a date with Dr.Burke? Why? Why? Why...
我觉得好纠结
should that bother me?
我喜欢那家伙 他就像是
I, I love that man, he's like a uh...
爸爸的亲兄弟
a brother to Dad.
你只要知道他是我交往过的男人中
Well, for your information, he happens to be
最聪明 最优雅 也是最性感的男人
one of the brightest, most sophisticated, sexiest man I've ever been with.
柏克医生性感吗
Dr.Burke is sexy?
天啊      天啊
Oh, God!        Oh, God!
性感得突破天际
Absolutely!
日
Damn!
又是馆里找我 我可以...
It's the museum again, can I? Oh.
柏克医生亲过我一次
You know, Dr.Burke kissed me once.
什么时候
When?
7岁时我骑自行车 摔倒在他家门口
When I was um, 7, I crashed my bike right out in front of his house
为了让我不哭 他在我这里亲了一下
and to stop me from crying, he kissed me right here.
你太幸福了
Oh, you are so lucky!
那是
I know.
南方古猿不应该放在那个展区
Woah, woah, woah, australopithecus isn't supposed to be in that display.
不 不
No, no.
不 能人是能竖起来的 南方古猿从来都不能竖起来
No, no, Homo habilis was erect, australopithecus was never fully erect.
或许是他紧张了
Well, maybe he was nervous.
瞧瞧 我真不敢相信
Oh, look, I can't believe this.
能人根本还没学会使用工具
Homo habilis hasn't even learned how to use tools yet
他们竟然还把陶壶跟他放一起
and they've got him here wi, with clay pots.
不如直接给他个微波炉算了
Why don't, why don't they just give him a microwave?
抱歉耽误了这么久
I'm sorry, I'm sorry this is taking so long.
这比我预期中还花时间 我们还是可以去吃晚餐的
You know, I, I, it's just, it's longer than I expected, we will have dinner
没关系的
It's okay, it's fine.
卡尔!
Karl!
天啊
Oh, God.
喔噢 这是蜜雪儿吗      是的
Wow! Is that Michelle?        Yep.
高中毕业后就没见过她了
I've not seen her since high school graduation.
天呐 那天晚上她喝得很...
Oh my God, that night she got so dru...
带感儿
Motional.
她又要生了
You know, she's having another baby.
我以为她才生过
I thought she just had one.
不 亨利快两岁了
No no, Henry's almost 2.
他讲话啊什么的都会 看
And he's talking and everything. Here.
知道吗 前几天他告诉我 他喜欢我胜过他爷爷
You know, the other day he told me he liked me better than his other grandpa.
公平来说 他爷爷是酒鬼 但还是...
Now in all fairness, his other grandpa's a drunk, but still...
哎 你是爷爷辈的人了
Whoa, you're a grandpa.
是啊
Yeah.
我们疯了吗
Are we nuts here?
不知道 或许吧
I don't know, maybe.
我是说 我在和一个曾在他泳池里尿尿的男人约会
I mean, I'm dating a man whose pool I once peed in.
我不需要知道那么多
I didn't need to know that.
我猜21年是差太多了
I guess 21 years is a lot.
日啊 老子能喝酒的时候你才刚出生
I mean hell, I'm a whole person-who-can-drink older than you.
是啊
Yeah.
那么...
So...
或许我们该...      是啊
So maybe we should just...        Yeah.
对
Yeah.
或许吧
Maybe.
喔噢
Wow.
这感觉太烂了
This really sucks.
可不是嘛
Yeah, it sure does.
我们不必现在就做决定 对吧
Well, we don't really have to decide anything right now, do we?
不 我们一点都不用急
No, no, there's no rush or anything.
披萨外卖      老娘要宰了那两个傻逼
Hey, the pizza delivery!        Oh, I'm gonna kill those guys.
瑞秋      好
Rach?        Oh.
都搞定了
I'm done.
好的 但是餐厅也打烊了
Yeah, well, you know what, so is uh, Sorentino's.
什么 噢 对不起 我们 呃 我们去别的地方吧
What, okay, I'm sorry, let's uh, why don't we find someplace else.
不用了 很晚了 餐厅都打烊了
No, you know what, it's late, everything's gonna be closed.
我们改天再去吃好了
Why don't we just do it another night?
不 不要
No, no, we won't.
不要?
We won't?
跟我来
Come on.
好 那是死的吧
Okay, that's dead, right?
这是什么 我们要干嘛
What is this? What are we doing?
嘘 你要红莓苹果还是红莓葡萄
Shh. Do you want CranApple or CranGrape?
葡萄
Grape.
好...
Okay, now...
坐下
sit.
好嘞
Okay.
天呐
Oh, my God!
"数十亿年前 地球只是..."
"Billions of years ago, Earth was only..."
抱歉
Sorry.
啊 我们在看什么
Ah, so, what are we looking at?
你看那边 看到大星团旁边的小星团了吗
Well uh, you see that, that little cluster of stars next to the big one?
那就是大熊座
That is Ursa Major.
真的吗
Really?
哥蒙的 也许吧
I've no idea, could be.
听着 抱歉我今晚还要工作
Listen, I'm sorry I had to work tonight.
没关系
Oh, that's okay.
你值得我等
You were worth the wait.
我指的不只是今晚
And I don't just mean tonight.
喔噢
Whoa.
你没笑
You're not laughing.
这次没什么好笑的
This time it's not so funny.
把结解开
Okay, loosen the knot, loosen the knot.
抱歉
Sorry, sorry.
啊 天呐
Aah! Oh, God! Oh.
亲爱的
Honey?
没关系的
Oh,that's okay.
什么
What?
噢 不 你只是压到果汁盒了
Oh, no, you just rolled over the juice box.
谢天谢地
Oh, thank God!
嘿
Hey.
早
Hey, you.
真不敢相信我会在你身边醒来
I can't believe I'm waking up next to you.
是啊 真是令人难以...
I know, it is pretty unbelie...
怎么了
What?
有围观群众
We're not alone.
是火灾警报吗
Is that the fire alarm?
对
Yeah.
地上还没热 我们还有时间
Oh it's not warm yet, we still have time.
很好
Cool.
【海盗美剧 友情制作】
-== http://www.hdmeiju.com ==-
新浪微博：@海盗美剧